Close your sleepy eyes, the daylight is done,
Resting quietly behind the sun.
Little stars are waking in the purple sky,
Singing a gentle, floating lullaby.
Teddy bear is cuddled right beside your chest,
Time for little tired eyes to take a rest.
Sleep tight, rest your little head,
Safe and cozy in your warm soft bed.
Drifting on a cloud so soft and light,
Sweet dreams, little angel, sleep goodnight.
Moonlight whispers softly through the windowpane,
Silver raindrops dancing down the sleepy lane.
Let your happy thoughts drift away to sleep,
Counting all the little jumping fluffy sheep.
Tomorrow brings another sunny day to play,
Now let all the sleepy dreams fly away.
Sleep tight, rest your little head,
Safe and cozy in your warm soft bed.
Drifting on a cloud so soft and light,
Sweet dreams, little angel, sleep goodnight.